healthinsurance.net 2013-05-09

# Privacy Policy

### Our Commitment to Privacy

At Healthinsurance.net, we are keenly aware of the trust you place in us and our responsibility to protect your privacy. As part of this responsibility, we let you know what information we collect, and this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") addresses how we collect, use, and share this information. By using Healthinsurance.net, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and our [Terms and Conditions for Use](http://www.healthinsurance.net/terms.html).

### Secure Site:

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. We use secure server software and firewalls as part of our efforts to protect your information from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed. By using our site, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks in exchange for the benefit of using Healthinsurance.net to request insurance quotes.

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as social security number, Driver's license number, national ID, personal health information) on our registration forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). When your information is placed through our secure online server, or you send us an email, our secure server software (SSL) encrypts the information you input before it is sent to us. The encryption of the information does not guaranty its security, as encryption code can be broken, however all of customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.

### The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the www.Healthinsurance.net website (the "Site"). On some Site pages you may request insurance quotes from a network of local insurance agents and/or companies and partners. We help consumers shop for insurance and various other products by connecting consumers with insurance agents or other vendors. By clicking "Get Quotes," you authorize and agree that we may use the information you share with us to help match you with insurance providers or other vendors. This authorization includes, without limitation, our providing your information to insurance agents, insurance companies, and/or other vendors who assist us in finding insurance agents, insurance companies, discount program representatives and/or other requested products or services (we refer to all of these as "Providers", and we sometimes refer to both consumers and Providers as our "users").

Insurance companies establish their rates using a variety of criteria. Because we deal with many Providers, the more detailed information you provide to us, the more accurate a quote our Providers may help you locate. The types of personal information that may be collected at through the Site include the following:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone Number  
And other information needed to develop an insurance quote for you

### The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide us to complete your request for insurance quotes. We do not share this information with outside parties except to facilitate your request for insurance quotes. By clicking "Get Quotes" and requesting an insurance quote, you acknowledge and agree that up to eight (8) Providers may contact you to provide quote(s) or to obtain additional information needed to provide your requested quotes. You further acknowledge and agree that each Provider that receives your quote request from the Site or our affiliates may confirm your information through the use of a consumer report, which may include your credit score and driving record.

You acknowledge that you have read and understand the Terms and Conditions of Use of the Site and agree to be bound by them. We are not responsible, and shall not be held liable, if a Provider or other third party to whom we have forwarded any of the information you submitted to us violates our Privacy Policy, or such third party's own privacy policy (if any), or otherwise violates the law.

To facilitate quote requests, you may elect to provide us with personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information generally means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, your name, home address, telephone number, and email address.

Examples of personally identifiable information may include:

First and Last Name  
Postal Address  
Email Address  
Phone Number  
Driver's License Number*  
Date of Birth

*While not required, this information may be helpful in processing your request to receive insurance or other quotations.

We process personally identifiable information as described herein and also for such purposes as:

To deliver our products and services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising;  
To conduct research and analysis in order to maintain and improve our products and services;  
Ensuring the technical functioning of our system and network;  
To aid us in developing new services;  
To alert you to product updates, special offers, updated information and other new services. (You may opt-out of these communications if you so choose.)  
To contact you in response to your requests for information; and  
To provide you quotes from up to 8 Providers who may contact you using the information you provide or to obtain additional information needed to provide quotes.

Further, we may aggregate information we receive from you and from our other users and may use or disclose such aggregate information to third parties in a manner that does not disclose any individual user's personally identifiable information.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may disclose information where we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms and Conditions or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other Site users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service and improve our services.

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. We use reasonable efforts to protect your privacy, however, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

We may also collect and use information from you when you voluntarily complete a survey, order form, registration page, or other form of data collection through any means, including but not limited to, U.S. mail, internet, wireless communications, SMS, facsimile, and telephone solicitations. Please understand that by providing such information, you are giving your express consent for Healthinsurance.net, its partners, insurance agents and affiliates to contact you through electronic means, mail, wireless communications, SMS, facsimile, or via telephone (even if your telephone number is registered on any national or local so-called "Do Not Call" registry). Such consent remains fully intact until Healthinsurance.net receives an email request from you with valid contact information rescinding such previously granted consent. If you did not give such express consent, or if you would like to remove such express consent, you may send such notification to [admin@Healthinsurance.net](mailto:admin@Healthinsurance.net).

Please understand that this Opt-Out Policy impacts only future delivery of solicitations to you sent directly by Healthinsurance.net on its on behalf. You may still receive solicitations from third parties. Such third parties may maintain their own separate databases from ours, and you will need to contact them directly to unsubscribe from each source individually. This allows you the freedom to pick and choose which subscriptions to maintain and which to discontinue.

### Our Commitment to Security:

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We cannot, therefore, warrant or ensure the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we use reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems.

### Third Parties:

We may enter into alliances, partnerships, or other business arrangements with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name, address, telephone number, and email for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think may be of interest to you. In connection with alliances, partnerships, or arrangements, we may also provide certain information to third parties. For example, some of our partners operate stores or provide services on our Site, while others power offerings developed by us for your use.

We also use third parties to facilitate our business, including, but not limited to, sending email. In connection with these offerings and business operations, our partners and other third parties may have access to your personal information for use in connection with business activities. As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution.

The Site may also contain links to other Internet web sites, including co-branded or other affiliated sites that may or may not be owned or operated by us. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites, including such sites' use of any information (such as IP number, browser type, or operating system) collected when visitors to the Site click through links to those sites. Even though such information might not identify you personally, we strongly encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of those sites.

### Your Consent:

By using our Site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. By submitting a quote request, you authorize the Site to provide your information to insurance agents, both local and national, and to our third party agent networks. You authorize these Providers to share your information with their vendors, suppliers, and insurance carriers in order to generate information for your quotes. By submitting a quote request, you acknowledge that the Site's service requires you to agree that our partner companies may obtain a consumer report or credit score from a consumer reporting agency (also known as a credit bureau) and that these partner companies do not have the right to obtain a consumer report or credit score without your written instruction-which you are granting by clicking the submit button on the Site.

By submitting a quote request, you instruct consumer reporting agencies to provide a consumer report or credit score on you to these partner companies. Where permitted by law, some insurance companies or their agents may confirm your information, through the use of consumer reports, which may include credit score and driving record.

### IMPORTANT NOTICE REGARDING CONSUMER REPORT PRACTICES

AS STATED ABOVE, BY CLICKING "GET QUOTES" AND SEEKING A QUOTE REQUEST, YOU AUTHORIZE AND AGREE THAT A PROVIDER MAY OBTAIN ADDITIONAL BACKGROUND INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO PROVIDE YOU WITH YOUR REQUESTED INSURANCE QUOTE OR POLICY INFORMATION. FOR EXAMPLE, CONSUMER AND/OR CREDIT REPORTS, OR DRIVING RECORDS, MAY BE ORDERED IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR QUOTE REQUEST. THESE REPORTS MAY PROVIDE ADDITIONAL INFORMATION THAT MAY ASSIST PROVIDERS IN DETERMINING YOUR ELIGIBILITY FOR INSURANCE PLANS OR OTHER PRODUCTS OR SERVICES, AND RATES THAT YOU MAY BE CHARGED. CONSUMER REPORTS MAY ALSO BE USED FOR UPDATES, RENEWALS, OR EXTENSIONS OF ANY INSURANCE YOU MAY OBTAIN. A PROVIDER MAY ALSO OBTAIN AND USE A CREDIT-BASED INSURANCE SCORE CONTAINED IN YOUR CREDIT REPORT. THIS INFORMATION MAY BE COMBINED BY A PROVIDER WITH INFORMATION YOU SUBMIT TO US, AND BY CLICKING SUBMIT AND SEEKING A QUOTE REQUEST, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU ARE PROVIDING YOUR WRITTEN PERMISSION TO OUR PROVIDERS TO OBTAIN YOUR CREDIT REPORT.

### INFORMATION TRANSFER AND SHARING POLICY

When you provide personally identifiable information to us, you do so for the purpose of our sharing this information with Providers to provide you with the quotes you requested and this information then becomes subject to each Provider's own privacy policy (if any). Federal and state laws provide limitations on the information practices of financial institutions such as insurance companies. Providers and others to whom we may forward your personally identifiable information may contact you with a quote by email, telephone, postal mail, or other forms of communication as permitted by law and you agree to receive such contacts when you submit your information, regardless of the presence of your phone number(s) on any local or national no-call or similar no solicitation list. Please understand that because we are in the business of helping consumers and Providers identify one another, if you are a consumer and you do not permit us to share your personally identifiable information with a Provider, we will be unable to assist you and certain of our services and offerings will be unavailable to you. We expect our Providers to whom we forward your information to follow applicable laws.

### Other Usage and Offerings:

From time to time we may seek to make available additional offerings and services including those that may not be insurance-related. In doing so, we will strive to give our users choices about whether or not you would like to continue to receive future promotional or marketing communications from us either directly or on behalf of others whose offerings we think may be of interest to you. In identifying which offerings we think may be of interest to you, we may use and analyze information you have provided to us. If you choose not to receive such marketing communications, you may still receive certain relationship or transactional communications from us as described herein.

### Vendors and Suppliers:

We may provide personally identifiable information to or permit access to personally identifiable information by our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, vendors and service providers for the purpose of verifying data or where such access is incidental to their assisting us.

### Protecting Our Legal Rights and Other's Rights:

We do not otherwise share personally identifiable information about website users with third parties unless we believe using or sharing such information is appropriate to carry out a user's request or if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce our Terms and Conditions, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of the Company, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a legal or judicial proceeding or court order.

### Customer Testimonials/Reviews:

We post customer testimonials/reviews on our sites, which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the providing customer's consent prior to posting any such testimonial/review.

### Authorized Users:

We control and operate this Site from our offices in the United States of America. We endeavor to operate the Site system in conformance with the laws of Georgia and the United States of America. We do not represent that the Site is appropriate or available for use in any specific location. Access to the Site from locations where its use or contents are illegal is prohibited. Persons who choose to access this Site from other locations do so on their own initiative, and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable.

### Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and the Site should not be used by children under the age of 18.

### Site Changes:

Please note that we review our privacy practices from time to time, and that our practices are subject to change. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. All amended terms shall be automatically effective after they are posted on the Site. By visiting and using the Site, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use or access the Site.

### How To Contact Us:

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us.
